concertstudy.net 2014-10-30

# Medivation | Driven by science. Focused on life.

Medivation Internet Privacy Policy

This is the Medivation, Inc., Internet Privacy Statement for its Medivation web site. You can write to us at Medivation, Inc., 525 Market Street, 36th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94105. We can be reached by email at [info@medivation.com](mailto:info@medivation.com) , or you can call us at (415) 543-3470.

Medivation is aware of our visitor's concern for privacy when using www.medivation.com. We want to give our web site visitors the opportunity to know that information we collect about them and how they can limit the use of individually identifiable information beyond the purposes of which they first provided it. At all times however Medivation, Inc. reserves the right to disclose information where required by law or to comply with valid legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order), to protect the company's rights or property, including without limitation the right to transfer the data in the event of a transfer of control of Medivation, Inc. or the sale of substantially of all its assets, or during emergencies when safety is at risk.

Please be sure to read this entire Internet Privacy Statement before using or submitting information to this site. By using this site, you agree with the terms of this Internet Privacy Statement. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use and the disclosure of that information in accordance with this Internet Privacy Statement. Your use of this site is also subject to the Terms of Use for the www.medivation.com web site.

### Data we collect and how we use it

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
Personally identifiable information includes your name, address, email, telephone number, survey information, site registrations or any other information which might reasonably be used to identify you individually. Medivation collects personally identifiable information from the web site visitors only when it is voluntarily provided. We may use this information to respond to an email or other inquiry or request, to help improve our web site and our services, or to send updates or notices about our company and the products we offer that we think may be of interest to you. Personally identifiable information will not be sold, rented or exchanged with unaffiliated entities unless the user is first notified and expressly consents to such transfer.

Medivation may also combine the personally identifiable information you provide with other generally or publicly available information to help us identify visitors' preferences or interest. We may use the information to improve the content of our web site or our products and services. Again, we do not sell, rent, or otherwise share with unaffiliated entities any personally identifiable data we collect unless the user is first notified and expressly consents to such transfer.

Medivation does not set cookies for this site or collect any information via the use of bits of information deposited in the web site visitor's computer.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
The Medivation web server captures the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of each connection to our site and the specific web pages visited during that connection. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider so you can access the Internet and is generally considered to be non-personally identifiable information because in most cases it changes each time you connect to the internet. IP addresses may be used to diagnose problems with our server, report aggregate information, determine the fastest route for your computer to use in connecting to the site, and administer and improve the site. Although the IP address and related information collected is stored in the server log files, no individual is authorized to access those files for any purpose other than system maintenance. We may also use this information to help improve our web site and our services by better understanding our audience. Medivation may also collect non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form to track data such as the total number of visitors to each page of our web sites, and the domain names of our visitors Internet service providers. We may use this information, which remains in aggregate form, to understand how our visitors use our web sites so that we may make them better.

**Children**  
Medivation does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years old through this web site. However, if the parent or the guardian of a child under 13 believes that the child has provided us with personally identifiable information, the parent or guardian of that child should contact us at [info@medivation.com](mailto:info@medivation.com) if they want this information deleted from our files. Anyone under 18 years old should seek their parent's or guardian's permission prior to using or disclosing any personal information on this site.

**How you can control and update data about you**  
We want to be sure that we keep only the most accurate and up-to-date information about you in our records. Therefore, whenever you believe that your contact information needs to be updated, you can e-mail us at [info@medivation.com](mailto:info@medivation.com) to correct or update your contact information. You may choose at any time to remove your name, telephone number, and postal and e-mail addresses from the list we use to send notices or updates and elect not to receive correspondence from us by sending email to [info@medivation.com](mailto:info@medivation.com) .

**Data integrity and security**  
Medivation takes reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our site and to protect your information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. All information transmitted to this web site is secure to the extent possible using existing technology. You should keep in mind, however, that no internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from this site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Moreover, where you use passwords, ID numbers, or other special access features on this site, it is your responsibility to safeguard them.

**Links to other web sites**  
Medivation web sites may provide links to other web sites as a service to our visitors. These are web sites we believe may have helpful information. However, Medivation does not endorse and is not responsible for the content of third-party sites. Nor does Medivation have any control over information you may choose to provide to those sites.

The privacy policy described here does not apply to third party sites, even if they are linked to Medivation web sites. Other Internet sites you visit may have their own privacy policies or no policy at all. Other web sites might use personal information differently than our policy permits. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy policies of any site before providing any personal information.

**Changes**  
Because this policy is subject to change, you should check this Internet Privacy Statement regularly to see if there have been any changes. To view our Internet Privacy Statement at any time, visit www.medivation.com.

Questions about Medivation Internet Privacy Statement may be directed to [info@medivation.com](mailto:info@medivation.com) .

Top
